Finding Aid for Constance E. Cumbey papers, 1920-2004
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files
  - Group 1
    - New York Open Center 1989 (Box 11)
    - Nexus 1994 (Box 11)
    - Non-Lethal Weapons 1994 (Box 11)
    - North American Coalition on Religion and Ecology 1993 (Box 11)
    - North American Interfaith Network (NAIN) 1999 (Box 11)
    - Occult and World War II 1990-1993 (Box 11)
    - Occultism in the Church 1991 (Box 11)
    - Octagon Place, United Marriage Encounter 1991-1992 (Box 11)
    - Odinism and Satanism 1996 (Box 11)
    - Opus Dei 1989-1992, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Orthodox Jews 1992 (Box 12)
    - Orthodox Observer 1996 (Box 12)
    - Orthodoxy-Gnosis Magazine 1990 (Box 12)
    - Outcome-Based Education 1992-1998 (Box 12)
    - Paganism 1994-2002 (Box 12)
    - Paideia Education Plan 1992 (Box 12)
    - Paine, Thomas (Box 12)
    - Parental Rights 2001 (Box 12)
    - Parents and Teachers 1988-1991, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Parents Roundtable 1991-1993 (Box 12)
    - Parliament on World Religions 1993, 6 folders (Box 12)
    - Patriot Network 1994-1996 (Box 12)
    - Pax Christi 1991 (Box 12)
    - Pentecostal Movement 2000 (Box 12)
    - People for the American Way 1986 (Box 12)
    - The People's Network 1995 (Box 12)
    - Pew Global Stewardship Initiative 1994-1998 (Box 12)
    - PhenomeNews Newspaper 1992-1993 (Box 12)
    - Police 1993 (Box 12)
    - Pope John Paul II 1993-2001 (Box 12)
    - Population Control 1993-1998 (Box 12)
    - Population Research Institute (Box 12)
    - Power with the Divine (Box 12)
    - Praise Tabernacle Ministries (Box 12)
    - Prejudice 1993 (Box 12)
    - Presidential Campaign in 1992 and New Age (Box 12)
    - Preventing Child Abuse 1989-1990 (Box 12)
    - Prison Fellowship 1995 (Box 12)
    - Pro-Choice Movement (Box 12)
    - Pro-Family Forum-Florida 1992 (Box 12)
    - The Progressive Thinker Newspaper 1922-1923 (Box 12)
    - Project Yedid (Box 12)
    - Pro-Life 1988-2001, 1 folders (Box 12)
    - Pro-Life 1988-2001, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Pro-Life, Life Advocate Magazine 1993-1996 (Box 13)
    - Promise Keepers 1994-1996, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Promise Keepers, 'New Man' Magazine 1994-1996 (Box 13)
    - Prophets 1989 (Box 13)
    - Protest Groups 1985-1986 (Box 13)
    - Protestants 1992 (Box 13)
    - Psychics 1988-1994 (Box 13)
    - Psychopolitics (Box 13)
    - 'Putting People First' Newsletter-Detroit 1992-1993 (Box 13)
    - Quixote Center-Quest for Peace 1989 (Box 13)
    - Racism 1980-1996 (Box 13)
    - The Raelians 1992 (Box 13)
    - The Rainbow Nation 1982-1984 (Box 13)
    - Rajneesh Foundation International 1985 (Box 13)
    - Reed, Ralph 1996-1997 (Box 13)
    - Regent University 1990-1992 (Box 13)
    - Religion
      - Miscellaneous 1990 (Box 13)
    - Religion in Politics Newsletter 1995-2001 (Box 13)
    - Religion in the Public Schools 1990-1997 (Box 13)
    - Religious Education 1995 (Box 13)
    - The Religious Right 1996 (Box 13)
    - The Republic of New Africa 1993-1994 (Box 13)
    - Republic of Texas 1999 (Box 13)
    - Research Institute on Anomalous Phenom (RIAP) Bulletin 1994 (Box 13)
    - Revivals 1997 (Box 13)
    - Right Wing Movements 1992-1994 (Box 13)
    - Ritual Crime and Abuse 1992-1994 (Box 13)
    - Robertson, Pat 1980-2001, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Robertson, Pat 1980-2001, 4 folders (Box 14)
    - Rose, Seraphim, Fr. (Box 14)
    - Russia 1986-1995 (Box 14)
    - The Rutherford Institute 1992 (Box 14)
    - Saint Frances Cabrini Parish-Padre Pio 2000 (Box 14)
    - Saint John the Divine 1989 (Box 14)
    - The Salvation Army 1993 (Box 14)
    - Satanism 1985-1993, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Satanism and Rock'n'Roll 1992 (Box 14)
    - Save our Sons and Daughters Organization (SOSAD) 1987-1992 (Box 14)
    - Schuller, Robert-Hour of Power 1989 (Box 14)
    - Scientology 1965-1991, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Secular Media-Media Spotlight Newsletter 1994 (Box 14)
    - Sensitivity Training (Box 14)
    - Separation of Church and State 1980 (Box 14)
    - Set Free Ministry 1990-1993, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Seton Home Study School 1992-1996 (Box 14)
    - Seven Ray Institute 1992 (Box 14)
    - Seventh Day Adventist Church 1990 (Box 14)
    - Sex and Teenagers 1993 (Box 14)
    - Sex Education 1984-2004 (Box 14)
    - Siloist Organization (Box 14)
    - Smart Drugs 1992 (Box 14)
    - Socialism-Spain 1995 (Box 14)
    - Solana, Javier 1999 (Box 14)
    - Solar Plexus 1989 (Box 14)
    - South Africa 1986 (Box 14)
    - Spangler, David Reflections on the Christ, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Spiritual Counterfeits Project (Box 14)
    - Spiritual Frontiers Fellowship 1983 (Box 14)
    - Spiritual Intelligence (SQ) 2000 (Box 14)
    - Spirituality-Still Point, A Center for Spiritual Renewal 1989-1990 (Box 14)
    - Spiritual Unity of Nations 1984 (Box 14)
    - Stair, R.G. 1996 (Box 14)
    - "Star Wars" Defensive System 1984 (Box 14)
    - Stress Management 1990 (Box 14)
    - Suicide 1992 (Box 14)
    - The Swastika 1975 (Box 14)
    - The Tara Center 1989-1991 (Box 14)
    - Target Earth 1989-1992, 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Technology and Alvin Toffler 1984-1991 (Box 15)
    - Temple of Understanding: Global Interfaith Association 1991 (Box 15)
    - The Theosophical Society 1934-2002, 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Theosophical Publishing House (Box 15)
    - Therapeutic Touch 1994-1997, 4 folders (Box 15)
    - Top Secret/Apotheosis: Multi-lateral Set of Hypothesis 1990 (Box 15)
    - Tort Law and Religion 1989 (Box 15)
    - Townsend, William Cameron 2000, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Tradition, Family, and Property Magazine 1995 (Box 15)
    - Transpersonal Psychology 1982 (Box 15)
    - Trent for Parish Priests 1972 (Box 15)
    - The Trilateral Commission (TLC) 1981 (Box 15)
    - Trust, Lucis Trust 1991-2001 (Box 15)
    - Turner, Ted 1989-1992 (Box 15)
    - Tyndale Theological Seminary and Biblical Institute 1992-1994 (Box 15)
    - Unidentified Flying Objects (UFO's) 1989-1994 (Box 15)
    - UFO Newsletter 1992 (Box 15)
    - The Unification Church 1980-1998 (Box 15)
    - United Methodist Church-Iowa 1992 (Box 15)
    - The United Nations (Box 15)
    - United States Economy 1994 (Box 15)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists (Box 15)
    - Universal Church 1984-1989 (Box 15)
    - The Urantia Foundation 1982-1991 (Box 15)
    - Vatican Voices Newsletter 1986-1987 (Box 15)
    - Vegetarianism 1992 (Box 15)
    - Vineyard Christian Fellowship of Seattle 1995 (Box 15)
    - Vineyard Ministries International 1995 (Box 15)
    - Violence 1985-1994 (Box 16)
    - Walt Disney Company 1997 (Box 16)
    - War on Fundamentalists 1990 (Box 16)
    - War on Iraq 2003 (Box 16)
    - Wellness Programs 1984-1985 (Box 16)
    - The Wesak Festival 1984 (Box 16)
    - The Western Review Institute 1990-1991 (Box 16)
    - White Supremacy 1990-1998, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - White Supremacy-Stormfront Website 1995 (Box 16)
    - Whole Life Monthly 1987 (Box 16)
    - Wiccans 1986-2000 (Box 16)
    - Windstar Foundation 1992 (Box 16)
    - Women and the Church 1992-1996 (Box 16)
    - Women and the United Nations 1995 (Box 16)
    - Women's Peace Journal 'Sacred River' 1992 (Box 16)
    - Women's Studies 1997 (Box 16)
    - Women's Theological Center 1991 (Box 16)
    - Word-of-Faith Doctrine and Benny Hinn 1993-1997 (Box 16)
    - Word of God Movement 1942-1989 (Box 16)
    - World Challenge, Inc. 1989-1992 (Box 16)
    - World Christian Movement 1995 (Box 16)
    - The World Church-Temple of Understanding 1962-1968 (Box 16)
    - World Congress on Evangelism (Box 16)
    - World Core Curriculum 1989-1991 (Box 16)
    - World Culture 1951 (Box 16)
    - World Economic Forum 1991 (Box 16)
    - World Economic Review 1987-1988 (Box 16)
    - World Economy 1961 (Box 16)
    - World Food Summit 1996 (Box 16)
    - World Future Society 1993-1998 (Box 16)
    - The World Game (Box 16)
    - World Game Institute 1995 (Box 16)
    - World Government 1995 (Box 16)
    - World Parliament of Religions 1993-1994, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - World Peace Prayer Society 1986-2001 (Box 16)
    - World Peace Tax Fund 1984 (Box 16)
    - World Radio 1994 (Box 16)
    - World Religion 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - World Unity 1989-1990 (Box 16)
    - World Vision International 1985-1995 (Box 16)
    - The World Wide Blood Protein Research Foundation 1983 (Box 16)
    - World Wilderness Congress 1987 (Box 16)
    - Yoga 1933-1995 (Box 16)
    - Zen Mountain Monastery 1988 (Box 16)
    - Zionism (Box 16)
  - Group 2
    This topical files subseries, designated Group 2, is the largest of the three subject subseries (62 linear feet; bulk dates 1980-1988). The content is much the same as Group 1, except that the files date somewhat earlier and have a broader range of subject headings. Additional topics covered here include the ministry of Pat Robertson, the Theosophical Society, Freemasonry, and a variety of conspiracy topics such as the "cashless society." The Lucis Trust, which was founded by occultist Alice Bailey and has consultant status with the United Nations Economic and Social Council, is also prominently featured in this series. Materials related to Nazism, White Supremacy, and the Christian Identity Movement are also present. Another strength of this group of files, as well as Group 1, is the topic of how the New Age Movement may have influenced the creation of new educational measures. Files about AIDS (some materials were filed under Homosexuality) capture the reactions and responses to the pandemic as it was unfolding in the early 1980's.
    - Albonic Consulting (Alpine Enterprises) (Box 17)
    - Abortion (Box 17)
    - Larry Abraham's Inside Report (Box 17)
    - Abundant Life Seeds Foundation, Port Townsend, WA. (Box 17)
    - Academy for Future Science, Los Gatos, CA. (Box 17)
    - Accuracy In Media (Box 17)
    - Action Life Publications, Santa Fe, NM. (Box 17)
    - Acupuncture (Box 17)
    - Mortimer Adler (Box 17)
    - Adventists For America (Box 17)
    - Aesthetic Realism Foundation (Box 17)
    - Aetherius Society (Box 17)
    - African National Conference (Box 17)
    - AIDS (Box 17)
    - Aikido (Box 17)
    - Akins et al v. New Mexico Board of Education (Box 17)
    - Alabama (Box 17)
    - Alamo Foundation (Box 17)
    - Alaska (Box 17)
    - Alban Institute (Box 17)
    - Alcoholics Anonymous (Box 17)
    - Alchemy (Box 17)
    - Gary Allen Report (Box 17)
    - Alliance for the Preservation of Religious Liberty (Box 17)
    - Altered States of Consciousness (Box 17)
    - Alternative Press (Box 17)
    - Alternative Technology (Box 17)
    - Alverna (Box 17)
    - African Academy of Pediatrics (Box 17)
    - American Arbitration Association (Box 17)
    - American Atheist Center (Box 17)
    - American Baptist Church (Box 17)
    - American Baptist Convention (Box 17)
    - American Bar Association Special Committee on Youth Legislation (Box 17)
    - American Bible Society (Box 17)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 17)
    - American Coalition of Unregistered Churches (Box 17)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 17)
    - American Farmland Trust (Box 17)
    - American Freedom Coalition (Box 17)
    - American Friends Service Committee (Box 17)
    - American Humanist Foundation (Box 17)
    - Americana Leadership College (Box 17)
    - American Leprosy Missions (Box 17)
    - American Natural Hygiene Society (Box 17)
    - American Opinion Libraries (Box 17)
    - American Paradigm Corporation (Box 17)
    - America In Prophecy (Box 17)
    - American Protective Association (Box 17)
    - The American Research Team, Beverly Hills, CA. (Box 17)
    - American Society of Cybernetics (Box 17)
    - American Vision (Box 17)
    - Amerika (the movie) (Box 17)
    - Amnesty International (Box 17)
    - Amway Corporation (Box 17)
    - Ananda: The Yoga Fellowship (Box 18)
    - Anarchist Association of the Americas (Box 18)
    - Anatole Fellowship (Box 18)
    - Mother Angelica (Box 18)
    - Angels (Box 18)
    - Anglican Church (Box 18)
    - Anglo-European Fellowship (Box 18)
    - Anglo-Israeli Theories (Box 18)
    - Animal Rights Movement (Box 18)
    - John Ankerburg (Box 18)
    - Anthroposophical Society (Box 18)
    - Anti-Apartheid Movement (Box 18)
    - Anti-Catholicism, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Anti-Christ Theories, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Anti-Christianity (Box 18)
    - Anti-Cult Legislations (Box 18)
    - Anti-Cult Organizations (Box 18)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith (Box 18)
    - Anti-Fundamentalism (Box 18)
    - Anti-Hunger Organizations (misc.) (Box 18)
    - Anti-Occultism (Box 18)
    - Anti-Semitism, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Anti-Semitism, Catholic (Box 19)
    - Anti-Semitism in New Age Movement (Box 19)
    - Antioch University (Box 19)
    - A Planned Deception (Box 19)
    - Apologetic Research Coalition (Box 19)
    - Apocalyptic Alert, Inc. (Box 19)
    - Apostasy (Box 19)
    - Apparitions (Box 19)
    - Aquarian Anti-Defamation League, Inc. (Box 19)
    - The Aquarian Faith (Box 19)
    - The Aquarian Foundation (Box 19)
    - Aquarian Revelation Center (Box 19)
    - Aquaria University of Maryland (Box 19)
    - Aquarian Network of Michiana (Box 19)
    - Corazon Aquino (Box 19)
    - Arcana Workshops (Box 19)
    - Arcane School (Box 19)
    - Archdiocese of Detroit (Box 19)
    - Arcosanti (Box 19)
    - Jose Arguelles (Box 19)
    - Arica (Box 19)
    - Aquarian Teaching Center Newsletter (Box 20)
    - Arizona, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Arizona Networking News (Box 20)
    - Arizona, Sedona (Box 20)
    - Arkansas (Box 20)
    - Ark of the Covenant (Box 20)
    - Armageddon Script (Box 20)
    - Herbert W. Armstrong (Box 20)
    - Art (Box 20)
    - Articles on the New Age Movement (Box 20)
    - Artificial Intelligence (Box 20)
    - Architecture (Box 20)
    - Ascended Masters (Box 20)
    - Isaac Asimov (Box 20)
    - Aspen Institute (Box 20)
    - Assembly of God (Box 20)
    - Assisi Activities (Box 20)
    - Association for Humanistic Psychology (A.H.P.) (Box 20)
    - Association of Political Risk Analysts (APRA) (Box 20)
    - Association for Research and Enlightenment (A.R.E.) (Box 20)
    - Association for Spiritual Evolution (Box 21)
    - Association for Transpersonal Psychology (Box 21)
    - Astara (Box 21)
    - Astrology, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - The Athanasian (Box 21)
    - Atheism (Box 21)
    - Athletes (Box 21)
    - Atlantic Council of the United States (Box 21)
    - AT&T (Box 21)
    - The Audubon Society (Box 21)
    - Australia (Box 21)
    - Austria (Box 21)
    - Avatars (Misc.) (Box 21)
    - Babylon (Box 21)
    - Bahai International Community (Box 21)
    - Alice Bailey (Box 21)
    - Bantam New Age Books (Box 21)
    - Banker Conspiracy Theories (Box 21)
    - Banking Developments (Box 21)
    - John Barela (Box 21)
    - David Barr (Box 21)
    - Bartering Schemes (Box 21)
    - Don Basham (Box 21)
    - David Bathurst (Detroit Waldorf School), 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Bayside Apparitions (Box 21)
    - Sylvia Beadleston (incl. Photograph), 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Bear & Company (Box 21)
    - Believe The Children (Box 21)
    - Don Bell Reports (Box 21)
    - Marilyn Bender (Box 21)
    - Saint Benedict Center (Box 22)
    - Fr. John Bertolucci (Box 22)
    - Annie Besant (Box 22)
    - Dr. Peter Beter (Box 22)
    - Better World Society (Box 22)
    - Beyond War (Box 22)
    - Bhagwan Shree Rajneesh, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Bible (Box 22)
    - Bible Believers Evangelistic Association (Box 22)
    - Bible Pathway Ministries (Box 22)
    - Bible References -- Prophets (Box 22)
    - The Bible Speaks (Box 22)
    - Biblical Criticism (Box 22)
    - Biblical Inerrancy Issues (Box 22)
    - Biblical Scoreboard (Box 22)
    - Bicentennial Projects (Box 22)
    - Mike Bikle (Box 22)
    - Bilderberg's (Box 22)
    - Kurt Billings (Box 22)
    - Biofeedback (Box 22)
    - Biometrics (Box 22)
    - Bioregionalism (Box 22)
    - Bishop Larkin Letter (Box 22)
    - Black Muslims (Box 22)
    - Helena Petrovna Blavatsky (Box 22)
    - Blavatsky, Theosophy (Box 22)
    - Samuel Blumenfeld (Box 22)
    - Bob Jones University (Box 22)
    - Body Electronics (Box 22)
    - Body Therapies (Box 22)
    - Bohemian Grove (Box 22)
    - Bollinger Foundation (Box 22)
    - Bob Bond (Box 22)
    - Drew Bonner (Box 22)
    - Books (Misc.) (Box 22)
    - Book Manuscripts (Box 22)
    - Book Quote Permission Requests Replies (Box 22)
    - Bob Bork (Box 22)
    - Bill & Penny Bowen (Box 22)
    - Boys Clubs (Box 22)
    - Brahma Kumaris (Box 22)
    - Brain Conferences (Box 22)
    - Brain Research (Box 22)
    - Brainwashing Techniques (Box 22)
    - Willy Brandt (Box 22)
    - William Branham (Box 22)
    - Bread For The World (Box 23)
    - Breckenridge Conferences (Box 23)
    - Harald Bredesen (Box 23)
    - Dave Breese (Box 23)
    - Breitenbush Community (Box 23)
    - Bill Britton (Box 23)
    - Pat Brooks (Box 23)
    - Brotherhood of the Cross and Star (Box 23)
    - Governor Jerry Brown (Box 23)
    - Rebecca Brown (Box 23)
    - David Bryant (Box 23)
    - Bubba Da Free John (Box 23)
    - Jamie Buckingham (Box 23)
    - Buddhism (Box 23)
    - Builders of the Adytum (Box 23)
    - Sunny von Bulow National Victim Advocacy Center (Box 23)
    - Maj. Edgar Bundy (Box 23)
    - Leo Buscaglia (Box 23)
    - Burklyn Business Institute (Box 23)
    - Elizabeth Burrows (Box 23)
    - Mrs. Butler (Box 23)
    - Dan Butts (Box 23)
    - Cabala (Box 23)
    - California (Box 23)
    - California: Berkeley (Box 23)
    - California: Bodhi Tree Bookstore (Box 23)
    - California: Fresno Area (Box 23)
    - California: Los Angeles (Box 23)
    - California: Los Angeles L.A. Resources and Forum (Box 23)
    - California: Los Angeles The Whole Person, A Calendar of Los Angeles Events (Box 23)
    - California: Misc. (Box 23)
    - California: Ojai (Box 24)
    - California: Orange County (Box 24)
    - California: San Diego (Box 24)
    - California: San Francisco (Box 24)
    - California: San Jose (Box 24)
    - California: Santa Clara (Box 24)
    - California Institute of Integral Studies (Box 24)
    - Calvin College (Box 24)
    - Joseph Campbell (Box 24)
    - Camp Farthest Out (Box 24)
    - Campus Crusade For Christ (inc. Audio Cassette) (Box 24)
    - Canada (Box 24)
    - Canada: British Columbia (Box 24)
    - Canada: Ontario (Box 24)
    - Canada: Ontario, Toronto (Box 24)
    - Canada: Winnipeg (Box 24)
    - Frank Capell (Box 24)
    - C.A.R.I.S. (Christian Apologetics: Research Info) (Box 24)
    - Carnegie Foundation (Box 24)
    - Jimmy Carter (Box 24)
    - Cartoons (Box 24)
    - Casanova (Box 24)
    - Cashless Society, 4 folders (Box 25)
    - Lu Castillo (Genesis Ministries) (Box 25)
    - Catastrophe Theories (Box 25)
    - Cathedral of St. John The Divine (Box 25)
    - Catholic Agitor (Box 25)
    - Catholic Charismatic Movement (Box 25)
    - Catholic Education (Box 25)
    - Catholic Evangelism Programs (Box 25)
    - Catholic Literature (misc.), 3 folders (Box 25)
    - Catholic Health Association (Box 25)
    - Catholic League for Religious and Civil Rights (Box 25)
    - Catholic Prophesies (Box 25)
    - Catholic Saints (Box 25)
    - Catholic Women: Church (Box 25)
    - Catholics for Truth In Education (Box 25)
    - Catholics United for the Faith (C.U.F.) (Box 25)
    - Edgar Cayce (Box 25)
    - Center of Concern (Box 25)
    - Center for Creative Pursuits (Box 25)
    - Center for Economic and Social Justice (Box 25)
    - Centering (Box 25)
    - Center for Peace Studies (University of Akron) (Box 25)
    - Center for Spiritual Awareness (Box 25)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions (Box 25)
    - Center for Theology and Public Policy (Box 25)
    - CIA (Central Intelligence Agency) (Box 25)
    - Gina Cerminara (Box 25)
    - Charkas (Box 25)
    - Channeling, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Charismatic Catholic Movement (Box 25)
    - Charismatic Renewal (Box 25)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank (Box 25)
    - Joseph Chess (Box 25)
    - Chi Power (Box 25)
    - Chick Publications (Box 26)
    - Child Abuse (Box 26)
    - Child Care Commentary (Box 26)
    - Children (Box 26)
    - Children of God (Box 26)
    - Children Reach-Out Efforts (Box 26)
    - David Chilton (Box 26)
    - China (Box 26)
    - Chinese Religions (Box 26)
    - Chinook Learning Community (incl. Photos), 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Chinook Learning Community Publications, "Warm Wind" Journal and The South Whidbey Loon. (Box 26)
    - Chiropractors (Box 26)
    - C.B. Chisolm, The William Alanson White Memorial Lectures, "The Re-establishment of Peacetime Society" (Box 26)
    - Cholera (Box 26)
    - Dr. Cho (Yonggi) (Box 26)
    - Christ For The Nations (Box 26)
    - Christian Reconstruction Movement (Box 26)
    - Christians Awake Newsletter (Box 26)
    - Christian Booksellers Association (Box 26)
    - Christian Bookseller and Librarian (Box 26)
    - Christian Century Magazine (Box 26)
    - Christian Chiropractor (Box 26)
    - Christian Chiropractor, "Holistic Nursing" Projector Transparencies (Box 26)
    - Christian Chiropractors Association (Box 27)
    - Christian Defense League (Box 27)
    - Christian Education (Box 27)
    - Christian Inquirer (Box 27)
    - Christian Legal Society (Box 27)
    - Christian Liberty Report (Box 27)
    - Christian Mysticism (Box 27)
    - Christian News Digest (Box 27)
    - Christian News Network (Box 27)
    - Christian Prophets of Jehovah (Box 27)
    - Christian Public Policy Council (Box 27)
    - Christian Reconstructionist Movement (Box 27)
    - Christian Science (Box 27)
    - Christian Service Centers (Clearwater, Florida) (Box 27)
    - Christian Technocracy (Box 27)
    - Christian Vanguard (Box 27)
    - Christian Voice (Box 27)
    - Christianity Today (Box 27)
    - Church of the Brethren (Box 27)
    - Church Changing Conferences (Box 27)
    - Church of the Divine Man (Box 27)
    - Church of God (Box 27)
    - Church League of America News and Views (Box 27)
    - Church of Religious Science (Box 27)
    - Church of Saint John the Evangelist (Box 27)
    - Church Universal and Triumphant, 3 folders (Box 27)
    - Church Universal and Triumphant, Elizabeth Clare Prophet (Box 27)
    - CIA (Box 28)
    - Citizens for Excellence in Education (Box 28)
    - Citizens Freedom Foundation News (Box 28)
    - Paul G. Citkowski (Box 28)
    - Cleansing Action Theories (Box 28)
    - Clown Ministries (Box 28)
    - Club of Rome, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Coalition for Religious Freedom (Box 28)
    - Coalition On Revival, 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Edwin Louis Cole (Box 28)
    - Cole Publishing (Box 28)
    - Dr. John Coleman (Box 28)
    - College of St. Thomas (Box 28)
    - Colonics (Box 28)
    - Colorado, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Colorado, Denver (Box 28)
    - Color Therapy (Box 28)
    - Charles W. Colson (Box 28)
    - Christopher Columbus (Box 28)
    - Committee for Biblical Inerrancy (Box 28)
    - Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES) (Box 28)
    - Charles Colson (Box 28)
    - Comic Books (Box 28)
    - Common Market (European Economic Community) (Box 28)
    - Commonweal (Box 28)
    - Communications Era Task Force (incl. Audio Cassette) (Box 28)
    - Communication Workers of America (Box 28)
    - Communism (Box 28)
    - Community Education (Box 28)
    - Community Organization (Box 28)
    - Compassion International (Box 28)
    - Computer (Box 28)
    - Computers / New Age (Box 28)
    - Conflict Resolution (Box 28)
    - Congressional Clearing House On The Future (Box 28)
    - Congress on the Bible II (Box 29)
    - Connecticut (Box 29)
    - Conspiracy Theories (Box 29)
    - Constitutional Reform Movements (Box 29)
    - Consumer Product Codes (Box 29)
    - Robert F. Conte Bar Complaint (Box 29)